





ABOUT ME

Full-stack software developer focusing on JavaScript technologies, most notably React, Redux, Angular, Node.js, Express and Koa. Skilled in Linux administration, Bash scripting, MongoDB, PostgreSQL and Redis. Seasoned remote worker experienced in managing geographically distributed teams.

EXPERIENCE

Full-Stack Developer

Hey DJ

Hey DJ is a web app that performs tracklist recognition in DJ sets using the ACRCloud music recognition API. You give it a recorded DJ set, it returns a list of tracks that the DJ played. I have built the whole application from the ground up and subsequently received a funding offer to get it into production, which is currently planned for Q3 2020.

React / Node.js / Express / MongoDB / Mongoose / FFmpeg / ACRCloud

Full-Stack Developer

Fitvid Tracker

Fitvid Tracker is a web app that helps users organize personal workout plans based on YouTube videos. I have worked on this project as a member of a 4-person team. My contribution was implementing an API client to connect front-end to the back-end, the scheduling system Google.

videos. I have worked on this project as a member of a 4-person team. My contribution was implementing an API client to connect front-end to the back-end, the scheduling system, Google authentication, Redux state management, and a significant portion of the front-end logic.

React / Redux / Node.js / Koa / MongoDB / MongoOse / Material UI

2016 – 2019 Engineering Program Manager Red Hat Managed the planning, development and delivery of 20+ releases of various Red Hat products.

Agile / Scrum / Kanban / JIRA / Linux / Java / JBoss / 3scale

2015 **Documentation Program Manager** Red Hat

Managed a team of technical writers responsible for documentation of various Red Hat products.

Agile / Scrum / Linux / Java / JBoss / DocBook / AsciiDoc

2014 – 2015 Content Strategist Red Hat

Provided strategic guidance in documentation planning for various Red Hat products.

Linux / Java / JBoss / DocBook / AsciiDoc

2012 – 2014 Technical Writer Red Hat

Authored and maintained documentation of various Red Hat products.

Linux / Java / JBoss / DocBook / AsciiDoc

2008 – 2012 **Technical Writer** Kentico Software

Authored and maintained product documentation of Kentico CMS.

ASP.NET / C# / MS SQL Server / HTML / CSS

EDUCATION

2020 **Software Engineering** Codeworks, Barcelona, Catalonia, ES

Immersive software engineering bootcamp focused on full-stack JavaScript.

2013 Master's Degree in Applied Informatics Faculty of Informatics, Masaryk University, Brno, CZ

Study field Service Science, Management and Engineering.

2011 Bachelor's Degree in Applied Informatics Faculty of Informatics, Masaryk University, Brno, CZ

Study field Applied Informatics.

CERTIFICATIONS

Certified ScrumMaster (CSM) Red Hat Certified System Administrator Certificate of Proficiency in English

LANGUAGES

Czech - native **English** - proficient **German** - basic

CURRENT CAREER GOAL

Gain experience to become a senior full-stack developer within a 3-year time frame.